export const general = {
    topic: 'Javascript',
    level: 'Intermediate',
    totalQuestions: 15,
    perQuestionScore: 5,
    questions: [
      {
        question:
        "Ordinary table salt is sodium chloride. What is baking soda?",
        ques:'',
          choices: ['Potassium chloride','Potassium carbonate','Potassium hydroxide','Sodium bicarbonate'],
        type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswer: 'Sodium bicarbonate',
        weight:'1',
      },
      {
        question:
          'Ozone hole refers to ',
          ques:'',
          choices: ['hole in ozone layer', 'decrease in the ozone layer in troposphere', 'decrease in thickness of ozone layer in stratosphere', 'increase in the thickness of ozone layer in troposphere',],
        type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswer: 'decrease in thickness of ozone layer in stratosphere',
        weight:'3',
      },
      {
        question:
          'Pollination is best defined as',
          ques:'',
          choices: [
          'transfer of pollen from anther to stigma',
          'germination of pollen grains',
          'growth of pollen tube in ovule',
          'visiting flowers by insects',
        ],
        type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswer: 'transfer of pollen from anther to stigma',
        weight:'2',
      },
      {
        question: 'Plants receive their nutrients mainly from\n',
        ques:'',
        choices: ['chlorophyll', 'atmosphere', 'light', 'soil'],
        type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswer: 'soil',
        weight:'5',
      },
       {
        question: 'Computer is connected to Internet by which device\n',
        ques:'',
        choices: ['Modem', 'Mouse', 'CPU', 'RAM'],
        type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswer: 'Modem',
        weight:'2',
      },
      {
        question: 'Which is smallest planet in our solar system?\n',
        ques:'',
        choices: ['The Earth', 'Mars', 'Mercury', 'Saturn'],
        type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswer: 'Mercury',
        weight:'2',
      },
      {
        question: 'General Election in India hold after how many years?\n',
        ques:'',
        choices: ['2', '10', '15', '5'],
        type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswer: '5',
        weight:'1',
      },
      {
        question: 'Which among the following teams has played World Cup (Cricket) final match maximum number of times, but could not win a single trophy?\n',
        ques:'',
        choices: ['England', 'South Africa', 'Sri lanka', 'West Indies'],
        type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswer: 'South Africa',
        weight:'2',
      },
      {
        question: 'The absorption of ink by blotting paper involves\n',
        ques:'',
        choices: ['viscosity of ink', 'capillary action phenomenon', 'diffusion of ink through the blotting', 'siphon action'],
        type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswer: 'capillary action phenomenon',
        weight:'5',
      },
      {
        question: 'OS computer abbreviation usually means ?\n',
        ques:'',
        choices: ['Order of Significance', 'Open Software', 'Operating System', 'Optical Sensor'],
        type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswer: 'Operating System',
        weight:'4',
      },
      {
        question: '\n',
        ques:'',
        choices: ['', '', '', ''],
        type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswer: '',
        weight:'4',
      },
      {
        question: '\n',
        ques:'',
        choices: ['', '', '', ''],
        type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswer: '',
        weight:'4',
      },
      {
        question: '\n',
        ques:'',
        choices: ['', '', '', ''],
        type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswer: '',
        weight:'4',
      },
      {
        question: '\n',
        ques:'',
        choices: ['', '', '', ''],
        type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswer: '',
        weight:'4',
      },
      {
        question: '\n',
        ques:'',
        choices: ['', '', '', ''],
        type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswer: '',
        weight:'4',
      },
    ],
  }